motorcycledaily.com 2019-12-14

# Motorcycle Daily Privacy Policy<

Enhance Partners LLC, producer of MotorcycleDaily.com and its related content and service sites, is firmly committed to respecting the privacy of our readers, those people who visit and/or use our web property. At MotorcycleDaily.com we appreciate your readership and value your personal privacy. We respect the personal nature of the information you provide us on our web site and acknowledge the importance of protecting this information. By using or accessing MotorcycleDaily.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. The following policy explains how your personal information will be treated. Please check back periodically, as these policies may change from time to time; however, our fundamental commitment to protecting reader privacy will not change.

**Minors; COPPA Compliance**   
We do not knowingly market to or solicit information from persons under 18.  We do not knowingly collect, solicit or store personal information, even in aggregate, from anyone under the age of 18 or knowingly allow such persons to enter our promotions. If you are under 18, please do not send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a person under age 18, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a minor under 18, please contact us. 

**Site Visit Information**   
We gather analytics information on site activity, such as the reader's domain name/IP address (e.g., whether the reader is logged on from netscape.com or yale.edu), referral data (e.g., the address of the last URL a reader visited prior to clicking through to our site), and browser/platform type (e.g., a Netscape browser on a Macintosh platform) using Google Analytics. We use this information on an aggregate, anonymous basis, to improve site content and target advertising. We also may disclose aggregated information (for example, the percentage of our readers visiting the product reviews section) to third parties. When we do present such aggregated site activity to third parties, no one will be able to identify you or contact you.

**Links**   
Our site contains links to other sites, such as those of our advertisers.  We provide these links solely as a convenience to our readers.  Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites, including the accuracy, completeness, reliability or suitability of the information. We encourage our readers to be aware when they leave our site and strongly recommend that you read the privacy policies of such other sites, as such other sites may collect information about you. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by MotorcycleDaily.com. **  
**

**Third Party Advertising**   
Advertisements that appear on MotorcycleDaily.com are sometimes delivered (or "served") directly to users by third party advertisers. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. These third party advertisers may also download cookies to your computer, or use other technologies such as JavaScript and "web beacons" (also known as "1x1 gifs") to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. Doing this allows the advertising network to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement in order to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. In this way, they may compile information about where individuals using your computer or browser saw their advertisements and determine which advertisements are clicked. MotorcycleDaily.com does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers. Third party advertisers have no access to your personal information unless you choose to share it with them.

**Interest-Based Advertising**  
Some of the ads you see on MotorcycleDaily.com are tailored to your interests and based on your activity online or in the applications on your mobile device. This type of ad tailoring — sometimes called "interest-based" or "online behavioral" advertising — is enabled through various technologies, including browser cookies, mobile advertising identifiers as well as other non-cookie technologies.  To help protect your privacy, we are committed to providing you transparency and choice for these activities.  For more information and to opt-out of interest-based advertising, please visit: http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/

**Cookies**   
Cookies are pieces of information stored directly on the computer that you are using.  Cookies can contain a variety of information, such as a simple count of how often you visit a Web Site or information that allows the customization of a Web Site for your use.  The use of advertising cookies sent by third-party servers is standard in the Internet industry. If you click on one of our banner ads, you may get cookies from our advertisers that allow the tracking of your response to our advertisements.  These cookies do not identify you personally and are solely for the purpose of assisting us in measuring the effectiveness of advertisements placed on our site. This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by MotorcycleDaily.com and does not cover the use of cookies or other tracking technologies by any of its advertisers.

**Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)**   
Advertisers on MotorcycleDaily.com may elect to use third party advertising companies to serve ads on our Web site, and in these instances may use a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs/action tags/pixel tags) to better manage advertising on our site. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies. Clear gifs may ping or alert the advertiser's server about the online movements of Web users. For instance, advertisers may place a clear gif allowing them to recognize an existing cookie on your browser if from the same service. The main difference between cookies and clear gifs is that clear gifs are invisible on the page and are much smaller, about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. Please keep in mind, we do not have access to any information collected by these clear gifs nor additional information they may be tied to by the advertiser. **  
**

**Comments on Articles**   
Any information you disclose voluntarily on our comments pages becomes public information. We cannot control the actions of our site users and advise you to use your discretion in sharing information about yourself on the Internet. All information sharing is optional and done at your own risk. Privacy is a very personal matter and we encourage you to be careful and responsible when disclosing personal information online.

**Revisions**   
We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy at any time. Non-material changes and clarifications will take effect immediately, and material changes will take effect within thirty (30) days of their posting on this site. If we make changes, we will post them and will indicate at the top of this page the policy's new effective date. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you through notice on our home page and registered users shall be notified by email. We encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy policy. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you.

**Copyright Provisions**   
This website (including, without limitation, text, wiki, photographs, graphics, video and audio content) is protected by copyright as a collective work or compilation under the copyright laws of the United States and other countries, and Enhance Partners, LLC, dba MotorcycleDaily.com has rights therein. All individual articles, videos, content and other elements comprising this website are also copyrighted works, and Enhance Partners, LLC, dba MotorcycleDaily.com (subject to the rights of its sponsors, licensors and licensees under applicable agreements, understandings and arrangements) has rights therein. You must abide by all additional copyright notices or restrictions contained in this website.
